[
    {
        "title" : "Famous St Nicks!"
    },


    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "I'm an American Actor & Film Producer, starring in movies such as The Rock, Mandy and Con Air",
      "answer": "Nicolas Cage"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "I'm an American Singer Song-writer with hit songs including Sucker, What a man gotta do and Rollercoaster",
        "answer": "Nick Jonas"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I'm a Serbian/American best-known for my contributions to the design of the modern alternating current electricity supply system",
        "answer": "Nikola Tesla"
      },
      {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "I was an English Golfer who won 6 major Championships ",
          "answer": "Nick Faldo"
      },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "I was the former leader of the Liberal democrats between 2007 & 2015",
        "answer": "Nick Clegg"
      },
      {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "I am a towering Serbian Footballer who scored the opening goal in the 2011 Legaue Cup Final",
          "answer": "Nikola Zigic"
      },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "I am an Australian Tennis Player who lost the 2022 Wimbledon Final",
        "answer": "Nick Kyrgios"
      },
      {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "I am a fictional policeman in Hot Fuzz played by Simon Pegg",
          "answer": "Nicholas Angel"
      },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "I am an English television and radio presenter best known for having hosted a variety of shows on BBC Radio 1 including my Drivetime show",
        "answer": "Nick Grimshaw"
      },
      {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "I am an English cricket commentator and former England cricketer who was a left-handed opening batsman. I played in 17 Test Matches and 100 One Day Internationals",
          "answer": "Nick Knight"
      }
]
  